teacher.org 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Teacher.org

LAST MODIFIED: November 9, 2016

## INTRODUCTION

Esyoh, LLC ( **"Company"** or **"We"** ) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes our privacy and data practices with respect to information we collect or receive relating to users of Teacher.org (the "Website").

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy.

This policy may change from time to time. See _Changes to our Privacy Policy_. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

For information on your choices and access with respect to your information, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_ and _Accessing and Correcting your Information_ below _._

## SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This policy applies to information that we may collect or receive across the Internet and other digital formats:

  * On this Website.

  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

  * When you interact with our advertising on third-party websites and services.

  * From third parties in connection with your use of the Website.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW WE COLLECT IT

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website. We may collect information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number ("personal information").

  * That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks.

  * About your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

 **We collect this information:**

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.

  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website.

  * From third parties, for example, our business partners and clients.

###  **Information You Provide Directly to Us**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes the information that you provide when you participate in one of our online contests such as scholarships for teachers or when you request further information. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.

  * Information that you provide when posting comments in public areas of our Website.

  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.

  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

  * Your search queries on the Website.

When you provide comments to be posted in public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties ("User Contributions"), you do so at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users of the Website who view your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

###  **Information We Collect Through Automatic Means**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, time spent on the Website, aggregated information, communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.

  * Information about your device, browser and Internet connection.

The technologies we use for automatic data collection may include cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will allow third parties to issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. Through third parties such as Facebook, Inc., we may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). See _Third Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies._

### Information We Collect From Third Parties

We may receive from our clients your name and email address that you provided to our clients in response to a request for more information, such as when you request information about a school or educational program. Our clients provide us this information for billing and reporting purposes with respect to our clients and publisher partners. We retain this information as long as necessary to resolve payment and credit disputes with our clients and publisher partners. We may also receive reports containing non-personal information from third parties such as Google and Facebook in connection with services that they provide for our Website, including Google Analytics and Facebook Pixel. See _Third Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies._

## USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

### Personal Information

We may use personal information that we collect about you or that you provide to us:

  * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests.

  * To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Website and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, and information regarding our scholarships.

  * To send you marketing communications from us that we believe may be of interest to you.

  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Website, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns.

  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  * For any other purpose with your consent.

### Other Information

We may use other information that we collect about you:

  * To operate, improve, analyze and manage the Website.

  * To ensure the Website functions properly.

  * To calculate usage levels of the Website, helping diagnose server problems.

  * To supplement non-personal information with additional information we receive from third parties, such as advertising segments to allow us to target ads to you that may be of interest to you.

  * For security purposes.

  * To facilitate navigation, display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the Website.

  * To estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  * To recognize you when you return to our Website.

  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We will not use data we collect for the purpose of determining employment eligibility, credit eligibility, health care eligibility, or insurance eligibility and underwriting and pricing.

At this time, we do not honor "Do Not Track" headers and similar mechanisms.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

### Personal Information

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and corporate affiliates. Esyoh, LLC is the party responsible for the management of the personal information used by it and its corporate affiliates.

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business.

  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Esyoh LLC's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Esyoh, LLC about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

  * Directly by you, on public pages to which you are able to post information and materials. Please note that any information you post or disclose through these services will become public information, and may be available to users of the Website and to the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your personal information, or any other information, on the Website.

  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions, including our scholarship terms; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

  * With your consent.

### Other Information

We may disclose other information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual:

  * To our subsidiaries and corporate affiliates. Esyoh, LLC is the party responsible for the management of the personal information used by it and its corporate affiliates.

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support and enhance our business.

  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

  * With your consent.

In some instances, we may combine other information with personal information (such as combining your date of birth with your name). If we combine any other information with personal information, the combined information will be treated by us as personal information as long as it is combined.

##  **RETENTION OF INFORMATION**

We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

## THIRD PARTY USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics, a Google Inc. web analysis service. Google uses cookies, text files that are saved on users' computers and allow the use of the online service to be analyzed. The information generated on the user's use of the online service by the cookie is generally transferred to a Google server where it is saved.

Google may use this information on our behalf in order to assess users' use of the Website, in order to compile reports on the activities within this online service and in order to render additional services for us associated with the use of the Website and Internet use. Google may use the data in order to create user profiles.

We do not control and we are not responsible for Google Analytics or any of Google's tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about the privacy and data practices of Google, you should contact Google directly.

### Social Plugins

Our Website uses social plugins ("plugins") provided by social networks, including Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus and Pinterest. These plugins are identifiable by their logos on our Website.

When you interact with a social plugin via our Website or you access our Website while logged into a social network, your device establishes a direct connection to the applicable social network's servers. This enables the plugin to receive information about your access to the respective pages of our Website. We have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin.

We do not control and we are not responsible for the plugins on our Website. If you have any questions about the privacy and data practices of any plugin, you should contact the plugin directly.

### Facebook Pixel

Within our Website we use the "Facebook Pixel" of the social network Facebook, which is operated by Facebook Inc. The Facebook Pixel allows us and Facebook to determine the relevant target audiences to display advertisements (referred to as "Facebook-Ads") in reference to potential interests of the users. We use the Facebook Pixel to display Facebook-Ads to users who displayed an interest in our Website. The Facebook Pixel allows us and Facebook to determine, whether our ads were effective and satisfactory for users by being able to comprehend users' actions before and after they were on our Website.

The Facebook Pixel enables Facebook to receive information and store a cookie on your device. The cookie allows Facebook to store the relevant information within your device and retrieve it for targeted advertising. Facebook may connect the data with your user profile within its network.

We do not control and we are not responsible for the Facebook Pixel or any of Facebook's tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about the privacy and data practices of Facebook, you should contact Facebook directly.

### Other Content or Applications

Some other content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services . They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control and we are not responsible for these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about the privacy and data practices of these providers, you should contact such providers directly.

##  **THIRD PARTIES**

This policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including our vendors or any other third party operating any site or service to which the Website links. The inclusion of a link on the Website does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates.

Please note that we are not responsible for the collection, use and disclosure policies and practices (including the data security practices) of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, RIM, Pinterest or any app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider or device manufacturer, including any personal information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the Website.

You should always read the privacy policy of any website you access or social network page through which you share information carefully in order to understand their specific privacy and information usage practices.

## CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

We strive to provide you with choices regarding your information. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable, delete or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may not function properly. When you disable or delete cookies you are also deleting any opt-out cookies you have set on that browser or device. You will need to re-set opt outs after you have disabled or deleted your cookies on that browser or device.

  *  **Targeted Advertising** \- If you do not want us to use information that we collect or receive in connection with the Facebook Pixel, which delivers advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can go to Facebook.com to view your options. We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. You can find and manage many online ad cookies from companies by visiting the website http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

  *  **Promotional Offers from the Company** \- If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt out by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [privacy@esyoh.com](mailto:privacy@esyoh.com). If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions.

## ACCESSING AND CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION

You may send us an e-mail at [privacy@esyoh.com](mailto:privacy@esyoh.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. If we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect, we may not accommodate a request to change information.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our terms of use.

##  **SENSITIVE INFORMATION**

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Website or otherwise to us.

## SECURITY

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect personal information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem. See _Contact Information_.

## CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website, do not use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website and do not provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@esyoh.com](mailto:privacy@esyoh.com).

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy and data practices, contact us at [privacy@esyoh.com](mailto:privacy@esyoh.com) or the following mailing address:

Esyoh, LLC  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
2647 Gateway Rd., Ste. 105-409  
Carlsbad, CA 92009.
